Hi, I'm David Spuddle and I'm making this
video because I want to know.
Do you know how to do wing overs?
Do you know that after full stall spin
and spiral exits, this maneuver is the
most important
of all if you want to begin acrobatics?
The understanding and mastery of this
basic maneuver will later help you with
loopings,
tumbling, corkscrews, and mac twist,
infinities and more.
Do you know how to do it properly?
Do you understand the dynamics behind it?
Are you able to make more than five
perfect ones in a row?
If not, would you be interested in a
video where I would explain you how to
approach it at
the beginning, how to mentally prepare
for it?
What are the safety reflexes, material
and thoughts you need to begin?
What are the dynamics behind it, and how
its mastery will accelerate your acro
progression?
If you need such a video, let me know by
posting in the comments below and I will
prepare
the most exhaustive video material on
wing overs you will have ever seen in
your lifetime.
Now let me show you how I do perfect wing
overs.